Zeeshan Ahmed



ytzeeahmed@gmail.com



+923352226633



linkedin.com/in/zeeshan-%F0%9F%91%89-ui-ux-designer-680b64230



https://bit.ly/3x7VNIh

Summary

Design Portfolio at https://bit.ly/3x7VNIh

#opentowork | Finding next remote position|

I craft beautiful and usable digital and visual experiences across web, mobile and systems!

- #8 years experience in design
- # Usability and class in experiences and design
- # Swift response and communications.

Result-oriented and highly motivated Interface Designer with over 8 years experience.

Portfolio Below:

https://bit.ly/3x7VNIh

Experience



Senior Product Designer

Upwork

Jan 2020 - Present (2 years 3 months +)

I have been working with top tier client via Upwork contract # platform services and looking for the next big remote position. Worked with top startups valued combined at \$7M such as CryptoMok, Egantly, Blobsi, Again, Bushpa, myHarry, Because and more.

- # Complete UX and Product Strategy Creation
- # Created Hifi Mockups and Complete Design Systems
- # Pitch Decks, Marketing Material and UI Components
- # Developer Guidance and Integrations
- # Websites, App and Product (Specialized support for Startups)

UX & Digital Designer

5four Digital

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020 (1 year)

Full Time Remote Position, Worked with amazing portfolio of clients delivering high quality work.

Designed sitemaps, user flows and UX personas

Conducted user research and creating mood boards

Created low-fidelity wireframes and sketches

Created brand guidelines, brand identities and design systems

Created Webflow templates for marketplaces

Designed High-fidelity mockups and visuals for web clients

9 UI UX Designer

Digi9 Creative

Mar 2017 - Dec 2019 (2 years 10 months)

Worked as a Product Designer for a portfolio of Clients across the World.

Illustrating design ideas using storyboards, process flows and sitemaps

Designing graphic user interface element & design systems

Build page navigation buttons and search fields

Develop UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites functions

Conduct layout adjustments based on user feedback

Adhere to style standards on fonts, colors and images

28 User Interface Designer

2 Dam Creative Pty Ltd

Jun 2017 - Oct 2018 (1 year 5 months)

Developed intuitive, usable and engaging interactions and creative designs

Solved briefs using contemporary, creative conceptual design skills

Constructed and maintained technical project specifications and design flow charts

Researched, evaluated and proposed software/project/website needs

Wrote and maintained program code to meet system requirements

Developed websites using CMS such as Wordpress, Joomla and Squarespace.

User Interface Designer Intern

Vodafone

Jun 2016 - Dec 2016 (7 months)

Education

Federation University Australia

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology May 2012 - Oct 2015

Licenses & Certifications



Google Certified UX Designer - Google

Skills

User Experience (UX) • Product Design • Presentation Design • Branding & Identity • Art Direction • Responsive Web Design • User Interface Design • Mobile Application Design • Product Strategy • User Experience Design (UED)